SENCHL BAYBAK

PROFILE

Contact Details:

Telephone- 07449859470 | e-mail- seno.35.62@gmail.com

I am a dedicated Assistant Business Manager in a Global Flagship store Harrods with over 8 years of experience working in customer service roles in retail and hospitality. This many years of experience working in teams of different sizes and different businesses allowed me to become a strong team player who can easily adjust according to needs of business. I don't like classifying myself solely as a manager because I believe it is more important to be a leader; I believe I am leader who can inspire others to grow and succeed, I can get my colleagues and staff to follow my footsteps. I'm seeking new challenges and opportunities to gain different skills and develop my abilities further.

EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT BUSINESS MANAGER, CLINIQUE (ESTEE LAUDER COMPANY)
HARRODS LONDON- NOVEMBER 2021-PRESENT

Support Business manager to lead, coach and develop team to achieve sales, service and operational targets. At the absence of the Business Manager I have to carry these roles by taking ownership of the business and reporting to the Area Manager. This is the top performing counter in London and one of the counters with highest turnover around the globe with average £1,6million revenue. I ensure that all the team members are aware of the KPIs, counter expectations and the plan we put in place to grow our business. Responsibilities also include daily and monthly planning of the business as well as carrying out performance reviews of consultants to set individual targets to grow skill mindset and enable everyone in the team to develop. I am also in charge of our social media platforms to promote business to wider range of customers and engage by creating social content.

COUNTER MANAGER, LIZ EARLE (NO7 BEAUTY COMPANY) LONDON-OCTOBER 2021-NOVEMBER 2022

The focus of the role is to plan, lead and perform the business according to company standards and KPIs. As the counter manager I am responsible for creating business plan monthly to set a guide and structure to our daily work. My main purpose is to get all team members on board to perform to their highest to achieve and exceed targets; this is done by daily team talks and briefings, making sure all the team members are

up to date with their learning plans and do on counter activities to push team members to be more active. I am responsible for creating rotas for the counter as well as all the administration work such as holiday booking of staff and tracking their performance.

Operational excellence is also another responsibility as counter manager; I have to make sure VM guides are followed and any VM items missing are ordered through correct channels. As well as VM I am responsible for stock counts, adjustments and orders to make sure customer needs are able to be meet at all times.

Lastly this role requires to be a true representer of the brand to customers, through following the company's service model. I have to engage customers, and make sure their needs and wants are meet by going that extra mile and giving them a luxurious service throughout their time with the brand.

BEAUTY ADVISOR, NO7 (NO7 BEAUTY COMPANY) LONDON – OCTOBER 2018-OCTOBER 2021

Working as an individual and as a part of the team to provide best service to our customers. The main focus of this job role is to represent the company to the stakeholders by finding their needs and wants and meeting their expectations with very high standards.

On daily basis there is tasks that needs to be accomplished such as cleaning, stock filling and counting, making stock adjustments and preparing the work space to welcome customers.

Me being a person who wants to move forward in my career I seek every opportunity to take responsibility. Some of the responsibilities I have previously taken on the role is working with new team members and mentoring them in the job also planning events for store take over of the brand.

BEAUTY SUPERVISOR, WATSONS, IZMIR/TURKEY – JANUARY 2017-AUGUST 2018

Duties of this role included, but not limited to; manage product stock in various brands and make sure daily counts and adjustments were completed, supervise and manage staff on beauty brands, support store with managerial duties and carry out sales plan for the beauty department making sure all the promotions and VM are followed according to company requirements.

SALES ASSISTANT, ROSEHILL FOOD CENTRE, SUTTON, LONDON-MARCH 2015-MAY 2016

WAITRESS, HACKBRIDGE CAFE, WALLINGTON, LONDON- OCTOBER 2013-FEBRUARY 2015

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PLYMOUTH - HNC COMPUTER SCIENCE- 2014-2015

GRADE-PASS

MODULES

- Programming 1
- Information Technology and Professional Skills
- Computer Systems
- Programming 2
- Quantitative methods for Computing
- Software Engineering and Human Computer Interaction

SOUTH THAMES COLLEGE- BTEC LEVEL 3 EXTENDED DIPLOMA IN BUSINESS- 2012-2014

GRADE: MERIT, MERIT, MERIT

CARSHALTON HIGH SCHOOL FOR GIRLS-2007-2012

GCE AS LEVEL-

• BIOLOGY - C

GCSES

- ENGLISH LANGUAGE- C
- ENGLISH LITERATURE- C
- MATHEMATICS- B
- BIOLOGY- B
- CHEMISTRY-B
- PHYSICS- C
- PHOTOGRAPHY- A
- HISTORY- C
- TURKISH- A*

SKILLS

Quick Learner

I am easily able to pick up information and learn how a job is done or how a device or system operates. For example when I started my job as counter manager I didn't have

anyone to show me how the systems the company uses works therefore I had to set up the required programs onto my devices and sign up to the systems such as e-learning.

Easy to adjust

It takes me no time to adjust to new places or people; I am able to build relationships quickly with others. When I moved to Turkey after university for a year I was able to adjust to their way of living and working. Even coming back to London afterwards I was able to find a new job straight away and get used to new workplace within weeks.

Lead others

Even at the job roles that I wasn't supervising or managing others I was always able to lead others. I had responsibilities such as setting events whilst working for No7 making sure all my colleagues were aware of aims of these events and knew their roles during these events. My personality is a natural leader as well; from a young age I have always liked taking responsibilities in every group work.